<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<Data>
<baseImgUrl>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/</baseImgUrl>
<Game>
<id>29429</id>
<GameTitle>Persona 4: Dancing All Night Disco Fever Edition</GameTitle>
<PlatformId>39</PlatformId>
<Platform>Sony Playstation Vita</Platform>
<ReleaseDate>09/29/2015</ReleaseDate>
<Overview>Persona 4: Dancing All Night "Disco Fever" Edition is a North American exclusive set and the ultimate collector's edition for Persona fans! Persona 4: Dancing All Night is a story-driven music game of the cult hit RPG Persona 4, developed by ATLUS. Replacing the RPG elements are dance battles that challenge players' dexterity and accuracy, as they tap out re-mixes of fan-favorite themes and brand new music tracks. The storyline continues from after the events of Persona 4, when the teenage mega-idol, Rise Kujikawa, returns to the city to re-take her show biz career. During that time, a strange video appears on the internet and the unfortunate people who watched it have gone missing! Members of Kanamin Kitchen, Rise's junior idol group, have disappeared and it's up to the Investigation team to mount a rescue mission - only they discover the same monstrous Shadows from the Midnight Channel. To make matters even worse, their Persona abilities are rendered ineffective, and the Shadows in P4D can only be defeated by dance, so bust out powerful dance moves to save the day!


Persona 4: Dancing All Night Disco Fever Edition Includes:
Persona 4: Dancing All Night Game
Persona 4: Dancing All Night Vita Pouch
Two CDs of Shoji Meguro's Music from Persona 4: Dancing All Night
Teddie Keychain (North American Exclusive)
Exclusive Persona 4 themed PS Vita Skin
10 Persona 4: Dancing All Night Wallpapers
Two Sets of DLC Outfits
Bonus Playable Song - Never More
Collectible Outer Box</Overview>
<ESRB>RP - Rating Pending</ESRB>
<Genres><genre>Role-Playing</genre></Genres><Players>1</Players><Co-op>No</Co-op>
<Youtube>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p3jw89oIjmQ</Youtube>
<Publisher>Atlus</Publisher>
<Developer>Atlus</Developer>
<Images>
<boxart side="front" width="1188" height="1500" thumb="boxart/thumb/original/front/29429-1.jpg">boxart/original/front/29429-1.jpg</boxart>
</Images>
</Game>
</Data>
