<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<Data>
<baseImgUrl>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/</baseImgUrl>
<Game>
<id>23505</id>
<GameTitle>Total Recoil</GameTitle>
<PlatformId>39</PlatformId>
<Platform>Sony Playstation Vita</Platform>
<ReleaseDate>07/09/2013</ReleaseDate>
<Overview>Look lively soldier, grab your gear and fall in line for the biggest, baddest, craziest and most explosive war game to hit your screens and assault your senses. Total Recoil takes arcade shooters to the max; it’s a warmongers delight, packing a deadly arsenal of kick-ass weapons, devastating explosions, mega bosses, and much much more into one dynamite package.Start as a lowly Private and work your way up through the ranks by blasting through wave after wave of gun-toting grunts, turrets, gunships, mega-tanks, mines and more. Arm yourself with a huge range of upgradeable weapons whilst raining down death and destruction upon your enemies by earning ‘Killstreaks’ including artillery, air support, sentry guns and smart bombs. It’s the most gun toting, flame throwing, rocket launching, barrel busting, chain-gunning, explosive game on the App Store. So, what are you waiting for?...FALL IN SOLDIER!Features• Explosively addictive arcade gameplay keeps you coming back for more. If you can see it, you can blow it up! • Upgradable weapons including Assault Rifle, Flamethrower, Chaingun, Cannon, Grenade Launcher and Missile Launcher• Battle your way through The Oil Rig and The Mighty Jungle• Unlock ‘Killstreak’ rewards including artillery strikes, sentry guns and dive bombing planes• Packed with multiple game modes including Operations, Rank Challenges and Endless Wave mode.• Collect reward coins to buy and upgrade your weapons, killstreaks and equipment • More explosions per square inch of screen than any other game.........ever!</Overview>
<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
<Genres><genre>Action</genre><genre>Shooter</genre></Genres><Players>1</Players><Co-op>No</Co-op>
<Publisher>Eiconic Games</Publisher>
<Developer>Eiconic Games</Developer>
<Images>
<boxart side="front" width="400" height="240" thumb="boxart/thumb/original/front/23505-1.jpg">boxart/original/front/23505-1.jpg</boxart>
</Images>
</Game>
</Data>
