<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<Data>
<baseImgUrl>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/</baseImgUrl>
<Game>
<id>25662</id>
<GameTitle>Dynasty Warriors 8: Xtreme Legends Complete Edition</GameTitle>
<PlatformId>39</PlatformId>
<Platform>Sony Playstation Vita</Platform>
<ReleaseDate>03/25/2014</ReleaseDate>
<Overview>The Complete Edition includes all of the content from both DYNASTY WARRIORS 8 and DYNASTY WARRIORS 8: XTREME LEGENDS, thus giving new fans the opportunity to play through both titles. As an added bonus, PlayStation®3 system Dynasty Warriors 8 save data is transferable across all platforms. 

DYNASTY WARRIORS 8 is a historical tactical action game that follows the stories of the kingdoms of Wei, Wu, Shu and Jin through the actions of historical military and political figures of the time as they fight to gain control over the Three Kingdoms of China. It features more than 40 completely new stages: verdant plains, desolate wastelands, sharp ravines, huge castles, and other breath-taking sites, giving stronger emphasis in the stage of these epic battles and inspired by ancient landscapes.

DW8 + DW8 Xtreme Legends content together in one game!
PS4 Functionality: SHARE and Touch Pad functions for the PS4; touch screen functions for PS Vita.
Cross-Play and Cross-Share between PS4 and PS Vita
Easily over 100 Hours of Gameplay: 218 Scenarios, 82 Playable Characters, and 492 Different Weapons
New Story: experience a brand new story based on the strongest and most-feared warriors - Lu Bu!
New CHALLENGE Mode: compete for high scores with players around the world
Co-op play: Offline and online co-op play for two players!</Overview>
<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
<Genres><genre>Action</genre><genre>Fighting</genre><genre>Role-Playing</genre></Genres><Players>1</Players><Co-op>Yes</Co-op>
<Youtube>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=egBRDNBBD80</Youtube>
<Publisher>Koei</Publisher>
<Developer>Omega Force</Developer>
<Rating>8</Rating><Similar><SimilarCount>1</SimilarCount><Game><id>20240</id><PlatformId>4919</PlatformId></Game></Similar><Images>
<boxart side="front" width="577" height="735" thumb="boxart/thumb/original/front/25662-1.jpg">boxart/original/front/25662-1.jpg</boxart>
</Images>
</Game>
</Data>
